MARAM ABU KHAMEES

Amman | 0780496078 maramyahya86@yahoo.com

I hope to get a new position in a well-established company or organization that improve my knowledge and give me more experiences. In addition to that give me the chance to develop and to learn new skills in order to be an effective part in my work team through which we can do the best performance for our company.

EXPERIENCE

English teacher Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Ministry of education, Amman

Provide feedback based on workload and classroom behavior.

Organize classroom lectures and coursework.

Team leader and customer service

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022

Medlines, Amman

support the agent by helping them and gave them all the information they need to support the customers.

monitoring employee performance.

communicating with staff about issues affecting their performance.

English teacher Sep 2018 - Jul 2020

Ministry of education, Amman

Organize classroom lectures and coursework.

Research new language teaching methods.

Collaborate with teaching staff and administrators to foster a good student experience.

Service Advisor Mar 2017 - Sep 2018

Crystel, Amman

Answer questions about service outcome after consulting.

Advise customers about product _ services and potential opportunity.

Help customers decide between the variety of options.

Call customers to inform them of changes in service or to let them know about offers.

Quality Control and Secretary ship.

Jan 2013 - Dec 2015

Adnan alkhudari, Amman

Worked for one year as a quality control and I gained good management skills.

Worked at the same company as a Secretary ship for one year.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree - English Language

Feb 2011 - Feb 2016

Zarqa University, zarqa

SKILLS

Use email and Internet, high communication skills, time management, Ability to learn and develop. Microsoft office (word, PowerPoint,, Decision making.